[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the word 'Допомагати' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "てつだいます"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the word 'допомога' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "てつだい"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the word 'Зачиняти' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しめます"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the word 'Вимикати' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "けします"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the word 'Відчиняти' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "あけます"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the word 'Спішити' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "いそぎます"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the word 'Очікувати' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "まちます"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the word 'Зупинятись' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "とまります"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the word 'Брати' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "とります"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the word 'Повертати' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "まがります"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the word 'Тримати' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "もちます"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'Вмикати' read in word?",
        "answer": "つけます"
    }
]
